[GROANS]
[SIGHS]
- Good morning, Leonard.
- Aah!
- Uh-huh.
- We have to stop by Pottery Barn...
(Sheldon:)...on the way to work.
I bought these Star Wars sheets.
(Sheldon:)They turned out to be much too stimulating
to be compatible with a good night's sleep.
(Sheldon:)I don't like the way
Darth Vader stares at me.
(Leonard:)I'm not going to work.
(Sheldon:)Just because your career's been stagnant
for a few years, that's no reason to give up.
(Leonard:)Sheldon, I was up all night
using the new free-electron laser...
...for my x-ray-diffraction experiment.
(Sheldon:)Did the laser accidentally
burn out your retinas?
(Leonard:)- No.
- Then you can drive. Let's go.
[LEONARD SIGHS]
(Leonard:)Didn't I tell you I'd be working nights and
you'd have to make other arrangements?
- You did.
- And?
(Sheldon:)I didn't.
(Sheldon:)Let's go.